{"doc_id": "L0C04FPK3", "sent_id": "L0C04FPK3-0", "tokens": ["Cholera", "blamed", "on", "lobster", "at", "Dominican", "wedding"], "token_ids": ["L0C04FPK3:1-7", "L0C04FPK3:9-14", "L0C04FPK3:16-17", "L0C04FPK3:19-25", "L0C04FPK3:27-28", "L0C04FPK3:30-38", "L0C04FPK3:40-46"], "token_offsets": [[0, 7], [8, 14], [15, 17], [18, 25], [26, 28], [29, 38], [39, 46]], "graph": {"entities": [[5, 6, "GPE", "NAM", 1.0], [3, 4, "AML.Unspecified.Unspecified", "NOM", "1.0"]], "triggers": [[1, 2, "blame", 1.0]], "relations": [], "roles": [[0, 1, "A1_ppt_entity_blamed", 1.0]]}}
{"doc_id": "L0C04FPK3", "sent_id": "L0C04FPK3-1", "tokens": ["Health", "officials", "say", "contaminated", "lobster", "has", "given", "cholera", "to", "dozens", "of", "guests", "who", "attended", "a", "lavish", "wedding", "in", "the", "Dominican", "Republic", "."], "token_ids": ["L0C04FPK3:51-56", "L0C04FPK3:58-66", "L0C04FPK3:68-70", "L0C04FPK3:72-83", "L0C04FPK3:85-91", "L0C04FPK3:93-95", "L0C04FPK3:97-101", "L0C04FPK3:103-109", "L0C04FPK3:111-112", "L0C04FPK3:114-119", "L0C04FPK3:121-122", "L0C04FPK3:124-129", "L0C04FPK3:131-133", "L0C04FPK3:135-142", "L0C04FPK3:144-144", "L0C04FPK3:146-151", "L0C04FPK3:153-159", "L0C04FPK3:161-162", "L0C04FPK3:164-166", "L0C04FPK3:168-176", "L0C04FPK3:178-185", "L0C04FPK3:186-186"], "token_offsets": [[50, 56], [57, 66], [67, 70], [71, 83], [84, 91], [92, 95], [96, 101], [102, 109], [110, 112], [113, 119], [120, 122], [123, 129], [130, 133], [134, 142], [143, 144], [145, 151], [152, 159], [160, 162], [163, 166], [167, 176], [177, 185], [185, 186]], "graph": {"entities": [[1, 2, "PER", "NOM", 1.0], [11, 12, "PER", "NOM", 0.5136476628199949], [12, 13, "PER", "PRO", 1.0], [19, 21, "GPE", "NAM", 0.48135023797729526], [4, 5, "AML.Unspecified.Unspecified", "NOM", "1.0"], [7, 8, "None", "NAM", 1.0]], "triggers": [[3, 4, "fouling", 1.0], [13, 14, "attendance", 1.0]], "relations": [[1, 3, "Physical", 0.4745639497746941, "Physical.LocatedNear"], [2, 3, "Physical", 0.5703102136588704, "Physical.LocatedNear"]], "roles": [[0, 3, "A1_gol_thing_becoming_contaminated", 1.0], [0, 5, "A2_ppt_contaminant", 1.0], [1, 1, "A0_pag_thing_attending", 1.0]]}}
{"doc_id": "L0C04FPK3", "sent_id": "L0C04FPK3-2", "tokens": ["Most", "of", "the", "nearly", "500", "guests", "flew", "in", "from", "Venezuela", ",", "and", "that", "country's", "health", "minister", "says", "Thursday", "that", "37", "of", "them", "have", "tested", "positive", "for", "cholera", "."], "token_ids": ["L0C04FPK3:188-191", "L0C04FPK3:193-194", "L0C04FPK3:196-198", "L0C04FPK3:200-205", "L0C04FPK3:207-209", "L0C04FPK3:211-216", "L0C04FPK3:218-221", "L0C04FPK3:223-224", "L0C04FPK3:226-229", "L0C04FPK3:231-239", "L0C04FPK3:240-240", "L0C04FPK3:242-244", "L0C04FPK3:246-249", "L0C04FPK3:251-259", "L0C04FPK3:261-266", "L0C04FPK3:268-275", "L0C04FPK3:277-280", "L0C04FPK3:282-289", "L0C04FPK3:291-294", "L0C04FPK3:296-297", "L0C04FPK3:299-300", "L0C04FPK3:302-305", "L0C04FPK3:307-310", "L0C04FPK3:312-317", "L0C04FPK3:319-326", "L0C04FPK3:328-330", "L0C04FPK3:332-338", "L0C04FPK3:339-339"], "token_offsets": [[187, 191], [192, 194], [195, 198], [199, 205], [206, 209], [210, 216], [217, 221], [222, 224], [225, 229], [230, 239], [239, 240], [241, 244], [245, 249], [250, 259], [260, 266], [267, 275], [276, 280], [281, 289], [290, 294], [295, 297], [298, 300], [301, 305], [306, 310], [311, 317], [318, 326], [327, 330], [331, 338], [338, 339]], "graph": {"entities": [[0, 1, "PER", "PRO", 1.0], [5, 6, "PER", "NOM", 0.4741100744308798], [9, 10, "GPE", "NAM", 1.0], [15, 16, "PER", "NOM", 0.4855323587915526], [19, 20, "PER", "PRO", 1.0], [21, 22, "PER", "PRO", 0.4855323587915526], [26, 27, "None", "NAM", 1.0]], "triggers": [[6, 8, "Movement.Transportation.Unspecified", 1.0], [23, 24, "intelligence_test", 1.0]], "relations": [[0, 2, "Physical", 0.719775157431958, "Physical.LocatedNear"]], "roles": [[0, 0, "PassengerArtifact", 1.0], [0, 1, "PassengerArtifact", 0.7700405898270627], [0, 2, "Origin", 1.0], [1, 1, "A0_pag_examiner", 1.0], [1, 6, "A1_loc_examined", 1.0]]}}
{"doc_id": "L0C04FPK3", "sent_id": "L0C04FPK3-3", "tokens": ["Eugenia", "Sader", "says", "four", "guests", "from", "Madrid", ",", "Mexico", "and", "Boston", "also", "have", "the", "disease", "."], "token_ids": ["L0C04FPK3:341-347", "L0C04FPK3:349-353", "L0C04FPK3:355-358", "L0C04FPK3:360-363", "L0C04FPK3:365-370", "L0C04FPK3:372-375", "L0C04FPK3:377-382", "L0C04FPK3:383-383", "L0C04FPK3:385-390", "L0C04FPK3:392-394", "L0C04FPK3:396-401", "L0C04FPK3:403-406", "L0C04FPK3:408-411", "L0C04FPK3:413-415", "L0C04FPK3:417-423", "L0C04FPK3:424-424"], "token_offsets": [[340, 347], [348, 353], [354, 358], [359, 363], [364, 370], [371, 375], [376, 382], [382, 383], [384, 390], [391, 394], [395, 401], [402, 406], [407, 411], [412, 415], [416, 423], [423, 424]], "graph": {"entities": [[0, 2, "PER", "NAM", 1.0], [4, 5, "PER", "NOM", 0.4549884626643329], [6, 7, "GPE", "NAM", 1.0], [8, 9, "GPE", "NAM", 0.4816262107579396], [10, 11, "GPE", "NAM", 1.0]], "triggers": [], "relations": [[1, 2, "Physical", 0.5808477729458299, "Physical.LocatedNear"], [1, 3, "GeneralAffiliation", 0.6550795237014984, "GeneralAffiliation.MemberOriginReligionEthnicity"], [1, 4, "GeneralAffiliation", 0.6550795237014984, "GeneralAffiliation.MemberOriginReligionEthnicity"]], "roles": []}}
{"doc_id": "L0C04FPK3", "sent_id": "L0C04FPK3-4", "tokens": ["The", "ill", "also", "include", "Dominican", "businessman", "Fernando", "Hazoury", ",", "whose", "family", "owns", "Cap", "Cana", "resort", "."], "token_ids": ["L0C04FPK3:426-428", "L0C04FPK3:430-432", "L0C04FPK3:434-437", "L0C04FPK3:439-445", "L0C04FPK3:447-455", "L0C04FPK3:457-467", "L0C04FPK3:469-476", "L0C04FPK3:478-484", "L0C04FPK3:485-485", "L0C04FPK3:487-491", "L0C04FPK3:493-498", "L0C04FPK3:500-503", "L0C04FPK3:505-507", "L0C04FPK3:509-512", "L0C04FPK3:514-519", "L0C04FPK3:520-520"], "token_offsets": [[425, 428], [429, 432], [433, 437], [438, 445], [446, 455], [456, 467], [468, 476], [477, 484], [484, 485], [486, 491], [492, 498], [499, 503], [504, 507], [508, 512], [513, 519], [519, 520]], "graph": {"entities": [[1, 2, "PER", "NOM", 1.0], [4, 5, "GPE", "NAM", 0.548948239428521], [5, 6, "PER", "NOM", 1.0], [6, 8, "PER", "NAM", 0.6373494111491144], [9, 10, "PER", "PRO", 1.0], [10, 11, "PER", "NOM", 0.6373494111491144], [12, 15, "FAC", "NAM", 1.0], [0, 2, "None", "NAM", 1.0], [4, 8, "None", "NAM", 1.0], [4, 8, "None", "NAM", 1.0]], "triggers": [[3, 4, "social_inclusion", 1.0], [11, 12, "ownership", 1.0]], "relations": [[2, 1, "GeneralAffiliation", 0.6133422702072923, "GeneralAffiliation.MemberOriginReligionEthnicity"], [4, 5, "PersonalSocial", 0.6133422702072923, "PersonalSocial.Relationship"], [6, 5, "Physical", 0.6133422702072923, "Physical.LocatedNear"]], "roles": [[0, 7, "A0_pag_agent", 1.0], [0, 8, "A1_ppt_theme", 1.0], [0, 5, "A2_gol_group", 1.0], [1, 9, "A0_pag_owner", 1.0], [1, 6, "A1_ppt_possession", 1.0]]}}
{"doc_id": "L0C04FPK3", "sent_id": "L0C04FPK3-5", "tokens": ["Dominican", "Health", "minister", "Bautista", "Rojas", "says", "lobsters", "for", "Saturday's", "wedding", "at", "an", "exclusive", "community", "were", "bought", "in", "Pedernales", "."], "token_ids": ["L0C04FPK3:522-530", "L0C04FPK3:532-537", "L0C04FPK3:539-546", "L0C04FPK3:548-555", "L0C04FPK3:557-561", "L0C04FPK3:563-566", "L0C04FPK3:568-575", "L0C04FPK3:577-579", "L0C04FPK3:581-590", "L0C04FPK3:592-598", "L0C04FPK3:600-601", "L0C04FPK3:603-604", "L0C04FPK3:606-614", "L0C04FPK3:616-624", "L0C04FPK3:626-629", "L0C04FPK3:631-636", "L0C04FPK3:638-639", "L0C04FPK3:641-650", "L0C04FPK3:651-651"], "token_offsets": [[521, 530], [531, 537], [538, 546], [547, 555], [556, 561], [562, 566], [567, 575], [576, 579], [580, 590], [591, 598], [599, 601], [602, 604], [605, 614], [615, 624], [625, 629], [630, 636], [637, 639], [640, 650], [650, 651]], "graph": {"entities": [[0, 1, "GPE", "NAM", 1.0], [2, 3, "PER", "NOM", 0.6920230554787211], [3, 5, "PER", "NAM", 1.0], [13, 14, "PER", "NOM", 0.5208523416358838], [17, 18, "GPE", "NAM", 1.0], [6, 7, "AML.Unspecified.Unspecified", "NOM", "1.0"], [0, 5, "None", "NAM", 1.0]], "triggers": [[15, 16, "buy", 1.0]], "relations": [[1, 0, "OrganizationAffiliation", 1.0, "OrganizationAffiliation.EmploymentMembership"]], "roles": [[0, 6, "A0_pag_buyer", 1.0], [0, 5, "A1_ppt_thing_bought", 1.0], [0, 4, "A2_dir_seller", 1.0]]}}
{"doc_id": "L0C04FPK3", "sent_id": "L0C04FPK3-6", "tokens": ["That", "town", "borders", "Haiti", ",", "where", "more", "than", "3,000", "people", "have", "died", "from", "a", "cholera", "epidemic", "."], "token_ids": ["L0C04FPK3:653-656", "L0C04FPK3:658-661", "L0C04FPK3:663-669", "L0C04FPK3:671-675", "L0C04FPK3:676-676", "L0C04FPK3:678-682", "L0C04FPK3:684-687", "L0C04FPK3:689-692", "L0C04FPK3:694-698", "L0C04FPK3:700-705", "L0C04FPK3:707-710", "L0C04FPK3:712-715", "L0C04FPK3:717-720", "L0C04FPK3:722-722", "L0C04FPK3:724-730", "L0C04FPK3:732-739", "L0C04FPK3:740-740"], "token_offsets": [[652, 656], [657, 661], [662, 669], [670, 675], [675, 676], [677, 682], [683, 687], [688, 692], [693, 698], [699, 705], [706, 710], [711, 715], [716, 720], [721, 722], [723, 730], [731, 739], [739, 740]], "graph": {"entities": [[1, 2, "GPE", "NOM", 1.0], [3, 4, "GPE", "NAM", 0.6300421129758811], [5, 6, "GPE", "PRO", 1.0], [9, 10, "PER", "NOM", 0.5401493764543349], [14, 16, "None", "NAM", 1.0]], "triggers": [[11, 12, "Life.Die.Unspecified", 1.0], [2, 3, "border", 1.0]], "relations": [[0, 1, "Physical", 0.9543651905273957, "Physical.LocatedNear"], [3, 1, "Physical", 0.9543651905273957, "Physical.LocatedNear"], [3, 2, "Physical", 0.9543651905273957, "Physical.LocatedNear"]], "roles": [[0, 1, "Place", 0.7158611379643], [0, 3, "Victim", 0.7158611379643], [0, 4, "AM_cau__cause", 1.0], [1, 0, "A1_ppt_thing_on_the_edge", 1.0], [1, 1, "A2_ppt_on_the_edge_of_what", 1.0]]}}
